http://www.dickgordonsports.com/privacy-policy

Log In
Search:
Privacy Policy
We use the information you provide to process your order, to ensure that your experience on our site is as enjoyable and efficient as possible and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.
Our primary focus and greatest concern is you, our customer. We respect your privacy and therefore have put this Privacy Policy in place to explain to you how we collect and use information in connection with our web site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the web site located at www.dickgordonsports.com.
The Information We Gather and How We Use ItIn order to fulfill your order and provide you with the highest level of customer service, we must ask you for personal information. The provision of personal information by you to us is always voluntary. DickGordonSports.com collects your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card information in order to deliver your order promptly and to the correct address. We use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation of your order. We will also send an e-mail when your package is shipped and include the shipper's tracking number. You may also choose to register with us. Registration provides advantages like faster check out; ability to store shipping addresses; advance notification on upcoming promotions; and exclusive invitations to private promotions and events. By registering, you can also update your personal information through your DickGordonSports.com account. When you purchase products from DickGordonSports.com or register for any DickGordonSports.com services, we automatically place you on our list to receive e-mail updates about special offers, new products, upcoming autograph sessions and new services. If you do not wish to receive e-mail updates, please see the Choice and Opt-Out section below.
Except as described in this Privacy Policy, DickGordonSports.com does not disclose, share, sell, or trade any personal or individual information that it collects from you to third parties, other than in the course of completing a transaction (including providing our contractors and business partners with your information if necessary to complete a transaction or service for you), providing you with information that you have requested, or in response to an investigation involving legal matters. We may also provide your personal information to trusted third party companies whom we believe may have products or services that interest you.
Our system automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on our Internet store. We do not use any of the navigational data that you - as an individual - provide while browsing or shopping on the Internet outside our web site. We do use navigational information in the aggregate to understand how our visitors shop in our store so we can make DickGordonSports.com better.
CookiesOur site also uses "cookies" so you can keep track of the items you have placed in your shopping cart. Each time you return to our Internet store our shopping cart will be just as you left it. We may also use and store information you give us (e.g, your shipping or billing address) so you do not have to reenter it each time you visit. Cookies are files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. DickGordonSports.com creates and then uses these cookie files to track your clicks and other data as you go through DickGordonSports.com.
Cookies enable us to provide features that simplify your shopping experience, such as storing items in your shopping cart between visits, saving and retrieving passwords, and recalling information on past purchases and other preferences. This will save you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to the DickGordonSports.com web site. If you do not want us to use cookies in connection with your use of our web site, you may configure your web browser not to accept cookies.
Choice and Opt-OutIf you do not wish to receive any information from DickGordonSports.com or our trusted third parties, please e-mail us at dgordonspt@aol.com. Once we receive your request, we will promptly remove you from our marketing list. However, we are not able to remove your information from the records of any third party who has been provided with your information as permitted by this Privacy Policy prior to such opt-out request.
If your interests or needs change in the future, please let us know.
ConsentBy utilizing the web site of DickGordonSports.com, you consent to the collection and use of this information by DickGordonSports.com as described in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to the Privacy PolicyIf the Privacy Policy of DickGordonSports.com is changed in any way, we will post the changes on this page for your reference.
Safety and Privacy of MinorsDickGordonSports.com does not intend to collect personal information from children under 13. If we discover that personal information has been collected from a child under 13 without the express consent and authorization of a parent or legal guardian, we will promptly remove such information from our databases.
Third Party AdvertisingWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. Our third-party advertising companies also separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
SecurityWe will make reasonable efforts to keep your information secure. However, we cannot guaranty that unauthorized access will never occur. Therefore, you accept this risk when providing us with your information.
LinksOccasionally, this site may contain links to other sites. DickGordonSports.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites. We suggest you check the privacy statement on each site that you visit.
Contacting the DickGordonSports.comDickGordonSports.com welcomes your questions and comments about our Privacy Policy. Please send an e-mail to dgordonspt@aol.com.
Effective DateThis Privacy Policy was last updated on May 18, 2011.
Home
About Us
FAQ
Store Policies
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Upcoming Signings!
© 2020 Dick Gordon Sports. All Rights Reserved. Designed by: GB Design StudioUse of any images from this website without written permission of Dick Gordon Sports is prohibited.   Follow us on Facebook
